<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sean Dockray</title><link>https://somethingilearned.today/</link><description>Recent content on Sean Dockray</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://somethingilearned.today/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>R.I.P. e-rat.org</title><link>https://somethingilearned.today/blog/rip-e-rat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://somethingilearned.today/blog/rip-e-rat/</guid><description>I recently lost my favorite domain, e-rat.org, which I have had for more than 20 years. It has played host to a few different digital experiments, a zine, one of the first sites of the AAARG library, and some attempts at real-time archiving of my own writing and artwork. Through that time, the web centralized into an uneasy ecosystem of a few social media platforms and an unknown number of more or less established traditional media (journalism, essays, etc.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://somethingilearned.today/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://somethingilearned.today/about/</guid><description>bio #Artist and writer Sean Dockray is a Senior Lecturer in Fine Art at Naarm&amp;rsquo;s Monash University, and his work investigates the politics of technology, focusing on artificial intelligences and the algorithmic web. He&amp;rsquo;s a founding director of Los Angeles non-profit Telic Arts Exchange, a space for local communities to engage with contemporary forms of media and art, and he initiated the knowledge-sharing platforms AAAARG.ORG and The Public School.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://somethingilearned.today/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://somethingilearned.today/contact/</guid><description>Contact #For academic matters: please contact me at the email address shown on my Monash researcher profile: sean.dockray@monash.edu
For anything personal: you can write to sean@somethingilearned.today
Social media # Strava: sean_dockray Chess: @errattus on Lichess @seandockray on Chess.com Github: @sdockray Mastodon: spd@post.lurk - although I&amp;rsquo;ve been more lurking that posting Facebook: @sean.dockray - I keep an account for connection to friends, family, and comrades, but don&amp;rsquo;t actively read or post to it.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://somethingilearned.today/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://somethingilearned.today/projects/</guid><description>Artworks and longer-term projects</description></item><item><title>‘All possible sounds’: speech, music, and the emergence of machine listening</title><link>https://somethingilearned.today/writing/all-possible-sounds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://somethingilearned.today/writing/all-possible-sounds/</guid><description>Attribution: James E. K. Parker with Sean Dockray.
Published: Sound Studies, Volume 9, 2023 - Issue 2: Forensic voices: cultures of sonic detection and identification in the West (Editors: Karin Bijsterveld and Anna Kvicalova)
“Machine listening” is one common term for a fast-growing interdisciplinary field of science and engineering that “uses signal processing and machine learning to extract useful information from sound”. This article contributes to the critical literature on machine listening by presenting some of its history as a field.</description></item></channel></rss>